Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see?
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand,
cut through the wind and make A stand,
don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone,
we'll go where we all want to go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
Sanji! Hey!
Stay focused!
Look behind you!
I'll finish you this time!
The hell?
What?
Did he just break Master
Queen's sword with his neck?
That's what I saw, but that
would be impossible, right?
I can't believe Sanji's neck broke
that sword in twain! Incredible!
Was that Haki?
What kind of power has he got?
You did that yourself
without armament, Haki?
Looks like I get to see
some germatech after all!
It's happening again. Damn.
Never seen someone with
a body like yours before,
but I do remember Judge going on about it.
I'll give humans exoskeletons.
And accelerated healing, he said.
I'll give them incredible strength.
And a heart of ice.
That won't be swayed by petty emotions.
I deeply apologize, sir.
I never should have offered
a dish so appalling to you.
Are you trying to leave
a scar on a lady's face?
I'm not like that.
I'm a human, not a cold-blooded
creature like them.
I'm not a monster.
Come on, you don't gotta cry.
Welcome to the Monster Club.
You are gonna fit right in.
Black Coffee Beam!
Ah, no!
Just give me a sec here!
I gotta figure out what's
going on with my body!
I need a little time to think, okay?
Try to remember.
What could have caused this?
You really like wasting
my time, don't you?
Was it because I transformed
into Silver Mask?
Really?
I used the suit a couple of times
and I'm losing my humanity already?
Something's wrong.
Why is he running away?
Hey, look!
It's one of the Straw Hats!
I guess he's scared of Master Queen.
He's talking to himself or something.
Just shoot him.
He's asking for it.
You're done for, Blackleg.
Time to eat lead.
Yeah, a bullseye. Nailed it.
I felt that.
His exoskeleton's top!
Show me more of your germ attack!
Put on the suit, be a pal!
Shut up about germa!
I got nothing to do with those maniacs!
I know you're probably a spy
for the Navy, but who cares?
I'm not sweating the deets right now.
All that matters to me is whether
you want to take down Kaido or not.
When this fight's over, the loser will be
dead and the winner will be busted up bad.
Perfect chance to send them
on their way, if you ask me.
you dig it there's room for one more we
can just snatch up the spoils and bounce
we're not loyal to kaido's army and we got
nothing riding on those
samurai either so there's
no reason for us to
fight how audacious you
really think i trust a
rotten backstabber like
you no offense but you're
not too trustworthy
yourself pal but we can
both trust each other
to act in our self-interest
if you want to hit
it big this is the best
chance you'll ever have
what are you laughing at don't tell
me you've lost your mind i know i've
cornered you but try to die with some
dignity did you eat
a smile fruit perhaps
what a picturesque tragedy brilliant
look guys over there are you okay killer
You guys!
What did you do to him?
Aw, kids, I can't believe
you sold out to Kaido!
You're gonna pay for betraying us!
No! Stop! Please!
Don't lay a finger on him, understand?
I forbid it!
What do you mean?
He's our enemy, right?
Why can't we help you?
In case you haven't noticed I've taken
your captain's life hostage From what I
gather he's fighting against Big Mom right
now already a losing battle one might say
You only have two options and I'll
gladly make the decision for you
Kill her!
Is this really the end?
We better think of something fast.
We're gonna have to bail if
the fire gets any closer.
We're back, Master!
As you can see, we brought Komachiyo!
We better hurry, that
fire's spreading fast!
It's a ghost!
No, a human legman monster!
Patty, someone help me!
Somebody Patty!
Anybody Patty!
Wait a second!
Slow down so I can catch you!
Whoever you are, please help!
I said, slow down, dammit!
Mind your hands!
You grab the leg of Kitemon!
Yeah, I know!
Do you want my help or not?
So it's not a ghost after all?
Is it human?
Perhaps a dream? Leave me!
I'm searching for my allies!
I am your ally, Kitemon!
It's me, your old pal, Usopp!
You can't hand me, you rogue,
for there is no time to lose.
That's a lot of blood.
Are you okay, man?
It's no use.
He can't hear us without ears.
We don't know where his head's at.
Yeah, you're right.
Then how do we let him know that it's us?
Remove your hands from my posterior.
Reveal yourself.
How is he talking to us without a mouth?
Farts.
Let's call it a special talent.
What fox he can't hear us I must
train and he can't see oh I got it here
The reverse crescent moon you
trace that on my posterior
that means you're an Ally
yeah how is easy please lend
me your assistance one of my
companions is In a terrible
state right now I'm begging
you please come to her aid
We can have Hamlet take us
there see you later Tama
goodness
I'm so terribly Popular today
head to the left tower on the
castle's first floor my ally is
in a crawl space there I know
not who you are but you have
my thanks okay legs count on me
That hurt like hell
what's happening to me?
You need to run.
Having a migraine?
What terrible timing.
You're too bad. Damn it.
Come here, Hera. Yes? Mama?
Napoleon. Ready, Mama.
Don't worry.
I'll help.
A kiss won't fix it, but your head won't
hurt after I chop it off. Come on! Fine!
Well, how about a thank you?
Useless!
I'm gonna die protecting you!
Stop getting in my way, you brat!
Now, shamble!
And counter-shot!
Mama!
How dare you do that to her!
Stolen fire!
Mama, Mama, Mama, Mama Ray!
Which one of you naughty
boys should I chop up first?
The quack who keeps getting in my way?
Or the half-dead, loud-mouthed rascal?
I've made it to the top.
I'm going head-to-head with an emperor.
If I end up dying here,
then what was it for?
You sure know how to make me laugh.
Hey you gotta get back up.
I wanted to kill you but it seems
like you're dying just fine.
No, I think not. Sorry. No!
What the hell is someone doing this to me?
Don't hurt, kid.
Let him go.
Let's make a deal.
Let him go, and you can
have my life instead.
No, killer!
You value Kid far too much.
You're better off without him.
You have suffered tremendously,
but all those misfortunes can
be traced back to your captain.
You don't get it, do you, Hawkins?
You never did.
Kid will surpass the four emperors.
He's gonna be king of the pirates.
Just stop already!
Defeating the four emperors?
Becoming king of the pirates?
What grand ambitions!
How admirable!
Then why are you getting in our way?
in your way am i then pick
up your blades and kill me?
i would accept your surrender you know i'd
even put in a good word
for you with kaido!
you're asking me to serve
that bastard after all this?
sorry i'm not as pathetic as you!
imbecile your battle was doomed from
the start you have no hope of beating an
emperor you've seen the beast you're up
against surely you understand now why?
they've ruled the seas for so
long your instincts must be
telling you to run for your
life any opposition is futile!
don't need to yell about it you can't
hide your regret you took the coward's
way out.
Regardless, if you bow to me, I
shall welcome you as my subordinate.
I get to bow
in quick.
You sacrificed your dignity to save your
life, but we never surrendered and we're
still here.
This tale has not ended.
You'll see which one of
us regrets our choices.
All right Then sink or swim I'll finish
this with no regrets
you'll get what's yours?
She won't last like this!
Nighty-night you Erica.
I have two questions for you.
What will happen if you take damage
somewhere that has no conduit?
Who does that affect?
What are you talking about?
I've made the nature of my
power perfectly clear to you.
There's no escape.
Any damage I take goes straight to Kid.
His straw doll exists inside me.
Every inch of his body acts as
my personal shield. Perfect.
Ah! Impossible!
How did you sever my arm?
The damage should have gone too.
Kid, he's missing an arm.
Remember?
No, I wasn't prepared for this.
The second question.
If I take this doll, how many
lives are left to protect you?
You've done well.
That was the last one.
The pain went away.
I don't understand.
straw man cards they're
upright the card of destruction
Beheading Claws!
Oh, no!
Hawkins!
The straw man isn't dead yet.
It will return if the cards so decree.
I shall reveal the true
ending of this battle.
The tower.
Spin and Sonic!
Kill him!
You did it!
I can't just stop!
Straw Man Card, The Tower.
It has two meanings.
One, the collapse of the old
Feeling better?
Let me see what I can do
about that Let's end this.
Funny, I feel light as a feather!
And the card's hidden
meaning, a new path forward?
Now go get her, partner.
Kiku, they're coming.
Just a bit longer.
How fortunate that I found an ally.
And more than that.
How fortunate that I survived.
Even after being chopped in half.
Perhaps my body was not
reattached properly.
After Sir Law cut it.
It is truly a miracle.
Now, I pray that my fortune holds.
So that Kiku may be saved.
Hello?
Is this on? Hello?
Hey!
Kanjuro!
Answer me, dammit!
Hey!
Can you hear me? Kanjuro!
It can't be.
That's Orochi's voice.
I am certain that I thoroughly
beheaded him in our last encounter.
It seems he does not know
that Kanjuro has fallen.
Hey, can't you roll?
Yes, Lord Orochi!
You barely breathing?
Were you defeated?
Indeed I fear this is the
end of my performance!
I see, rejoice!
You've done well!
You played your part to perfection!
I'm grateful!
I shall carry your kind
words to the next world!
Not yet, Contero!
Leeson, the crowd cheers for you!
and you hear them!
They're cheering for me!
Hello to me!
But my resentment has not faded!
It's not over!
Can you feel it?
Our ancestors!
They're waiting for a spectacular encore!
Now, raise your brush and paint it for me!
the Kurozumi clan's burning crutch!
We are not defeated yet!
The wrath of the Kurozumi
clan will come to life!
It will parade from this castle.
I see it now.
Walking deep into the abyss
until its fury is spent.
Then the place where it finds
rest at last will be our premium.
Only you can put our tired
spirits to rest, Kanjuro.
Give us peace.
As you wish.
Now, my most esteemed audience,
I present to you my final
performance, the Kurozumi clan
suicide rapid finale, Kazenbo!
Look, a fire!
He turned into a monster!
I have a report!
Some sort of giant apparition has appeared
on the second floor
inside the castle halls!
It's moving slowly,
but it passes through walls like
a ghost that seems to spread fire!
The castle is now engulfed in flames!
Give me, give me, give me
that germ-a-suit, yeah!
Give me germ-a-suit.
No need to worry about that.
I'll shut you up for good
there's
far
too much fire it's time to pull back we
can't stay here and fight I agree the
fire will cut off our retreat if we don't?
Hurry.
The Kozuki Klemn and its allies!
The Emperor of the Sea!
All of you should know that
pride comes before the fall!
Blaster!
Uh, ahhhhhh!
Ahhhh!
C'mon, C'mon!
Redheart!
H - H - H - H - H -